Profile

I am a skilled data analyst with a strong technical background in business intelligence and work history in data analysis. With around 2 years of experience in the field, I developed a solid grasp on business and strategy. Currently looking for a CDI (starting March '23).

Professional Experience

Data analyst

Naki Power

Jun 2022 - Dec 2022 | Paris, France

- Streamlined monitoring of KPIs for Operations/Marketing/Sales departments by designing and enhancing dashboards, resulting in significantly increased efficiency.
- Acted as primary point of contact for all data-related topics for 4 departments across 4 countries, including conducting in-depth analysis of business strategy.
- Advised and supported the Investor deck and data room design.
- Revitalized sales workflow by utilizing Google Places API data scraping to identify and prioritize potential leads (over 100,000) through classification and then feeding them through Pipedrive.
- Conducted A/B testing to optimize pricing strategy, leading to improved revenue per rental for services in Sweden by 50%.

Data Quality Specialist

Amazon

Jul 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hyderabad, India

- Conducted case-level analysis to identify predictors and root causes of business issues, leading to development of customer experience and delivery improvements.
- Generated data-driven reports and provided insights to stakeholders, facilitating informed decision-making and problem-solving.
- Analyzed metric issues related to customer delivery experience and identified root causes.
- Proposed viable solutions to improve performance based on analysis.

Education

Masters in Business Intelligence & Analytics (Msc, BAC+5)

ESC Clermont Business School Sep 2021 – Feb 2023 | France

Bachelor of technology in Computer Science

GITAM University

Jul 2014 - Jun 2018 | India

Skills

Programming languages (Python, SQL, Javascript, HTML, CSS, PHP)

Databases & Software (MySQL, Google BigQuery, Mongo DB, Snowflake, GCP, Google analytics, Microsoft SQL Server, Airflow, Hightouch, DBT, Asana, JIRA, Git)

Business Intelligence tools (BI Tools) (Power BI, Tableau, Looker, Microstrategy, Stitch, SAP, Excel, VBA, Sheets, QlikView.)

CRM Tools (Salesforce, Pipedrive, Intercom, ClickUp)

Machine learning (Regression, Classification, PCA, Clustering, Recommendation systems.)

Project(s)

Instacart Customer Segmentation (Kaggle)

K-means clustering, machine learning, Python Identified customer segments according to their purchasing behavior and calculated the Customer Lifetime Value (CLV) for each segment.

Sahit Sharma BODDUPALLY

Data analyst



⊠ sahitsharma.boddupally@ gmail.com

\(+33 7 69 05 84 78

• Villejuif,France

Languages

English

Hindi

French

Interests

- Chess
- Football
- Cosmology

Soft skills

Proactive

Organized

Teamwork

Analytical